<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Eviz</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dash_board">DashBoardActivity</string>
<!--    <string name="facebook_app_id">361726031886816</string>-->
<!--    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb361726031886816</string>-->
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1563487833858057</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1563487833858057</string>
    <string name="privacy_text"><![CDATA[<!DOCTYPE html> <html>  <!-- body -->  <body>   <!-- main container --> <div class=\"container-fluid\">   <!-- Terms --> <div class=\"row justify-content-center bgf5\" id=\"terms&conditions\">      <!-- scroller list -->  <div class=\"col-sm-12 col-md-12 col-lg-12 align-content-center justify-content-center\" id=\"termsConditions\">      <a class=\"scroller headScroll\" href=\"javascript:void(0)\">PRIVACY POLICY</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#version-and-Effective-Date-of-the-Privacy-Policy\">Version and Effective Date of the Privacy Policy</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#welcome-to-Use-Our-Products-and-Services\">Welcome to Use Our Products and Services!</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#applicability-and-content-of-Privacy-Policy\">Applicability and content of Privacy Policy</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#update\">UPDATE</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#collection-purpose-and-classification-of-personal-information\">Collection purpose and classification of personal information</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#scope-and-means-of-information-collection\">Scope and means of information collection</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#access-to-review-and-update-of-personal-information\">Access to, review and update of personal information</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#cancellation-of-personal-account\">Cancellation of personal account</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#use-and-setting-of-personal-information\">Use and setting of personal information</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#disclosure-of-and-making-available-to-public-the-personal-identity-information\">Disclosure of and making available to public the personal identity information</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#privacy-protection-in-bankruptcy-sale-merger\">Privacy protection in bankruptcy/sale/merger</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#privacy-terms-applicable-to-juveniles\">Privacy terms applicable to juveniles</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#law-and-Jurisdiction\">Law and Jurisdiction</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#risks-and-exemption\">Risks and exemption</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#storage-of-personal-information\">Storage of personal information</a>  \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#implementation-of-Privacy-Policy\">Implementation of Privacy Policy</a> \t  \t<a id=\"backToTop\" href=\"#terms&conditions\"><i class=\"fa fa-arrow-alt-circle-up\"></i></a>       </div>  <!-- text -->  <div class=\"col-sm-12 col-md-12 col-lg-12 align-content-center justify-content-center\" id=\"termsConditions\">  <hr id=\"version-and-Effective-Date-of-the-Privacy-Policy\"> <h3>Version and Effective Date of the Privacy Policy</h3> <p>Effective Date: 25/08/2020</p>   <hr id=\"welcome-to-Use-Our-Products-and-Services\"> <h3>1. Welcome to Use Our Products and Services!</h3> <p>Before using our Products and Services, please carefully read our Privacy Policy. <b>YOUR BROWSING OR USING OUR PRODUCTS SHALL BE DEEMED AS THAT YOU FULLY ACCEPT THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND COMMIT TO COMPLY WITH ALL APPLICABLE LAWS AND REGULATIONS</b> <br> “EVIZCARDS” or \"We\" refers to EVIZCARDS PTY LTD <br> You” refers to the users Whether you are registered or not <br> “Our Products” includes inbuilt software and services we provide to our users</p>   <hr id=\"applicability-and-content-of-Privacy-Policy\"> <h3>II. Applicability and content of Privacy Policy</h3> <p>Thank you for choosing to use Our Products and services. You may use Our Services in various ways. We hope you have a clear understanding of how we collect and use information and what kind of measures you may take to protect your privacy through our Privacy Policy. <b>IF YOU DON’T AGREE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DON’T USE OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES. IF YOU HAVE BEGUN USING OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES, PLEASE IMMEDIATELY CANCEL YOUR ACCOUNT AND STOP THE USE. YOUR BROWSE AND USE OF OUR PRODUCTS MEANS YOU ACCEPT THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS APPLICABLE TO YOU.</b></p>   <hr id=\"update\"> <h3>III. UPDATE</h3> <p>We have been continuously improving Our Privacy Policy, and with the extension of the scope of Our Products and services, we may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review our Privacy Policy regularly to know about it in its update version. If any update results in essential reduction of your rights under the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the reminder or announcement where it is notable at the interface of Our Products, or e-mailing you, before the date when the revised version becomes effective. <b>YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR PRODUCTS FROM THAT DAY ON WILL BE UNDERSTOOD AS YOU FULLY ACCEPT THE UPDATED PRIVACY POLICY.</b></p>   <hr id=\"collection-purpose-and-classification-of-personal-information\"> <h3>IV. Collection purpose and classification of personal information</h3> <p> <b>(a) Purpose of information collection</b> <br> We provide services to you by means of website, software and other applications. We collect your information only for the purpose of providing products and services to you (functions designed for each product differs from one another; you should familiarize yourselves with these differences and make your own privacy settings based on your needs and the circumstance), improving your experience of using Our Products and services, facilitating your use of Our Products and services more expediently, obtaining the information that you need in a faster and more accurate way, and conducting the commercial exploration of big data application, on condition of ensuring legal compliance and protection of privacy. <br> <b>(b) Classification of information</b> <br> The information generated during your use of Our Products and services may be categorized into the following two types by whether the information subject is identifiable or not with the information: <br> <b>(b-1) Identifiable personal information:</b> mainly including the information you submit, and it may be used to directly identify, trace, discern, and determine your true identity, such as e-mail address and phone number, etc. <br> <b>(b-2) Unidentifiable personal information:</b> mainly including the information generated during using Our Products and services, and it may be related to you but cannot be used to directly identify, trace, discern and determine your true identity, such as the records of your use of Our products and services.</p>   <hr id=\"scope-and-means-of-information-collection\"> <h3>V. Scope and means of information collection</h3> <p> <b>(a) Information you submit</b> <br> (1) Registration information you submit and the information collected based on industry practice and demand of the Products. <br> At the time you register your EVIZCARDS account, in order to identify the user and facilitate contact, you shall provide the real and effective information such as e-mail address of phone number, etc. You understand and agree that under necessary circumstances (e.g. cancel of account, etc.), we may identify you based on your registration information, so as to prevent any other person from using your identity to operate fraudulently which will affect your normal use of Our Products and services. <br> <b>(b) Data information you upload</b> <br> The information you may upload image and document during using our services can be your personal information or the personal information of others protected by laws and may related to your or other’s private information protected by law that may involve your or other’s privacy, or is granted protection under copyright law, etc. You shall guarantee that you have obtained the necessary authorization to copy and upload such data information. You will be required to make proper setting and adopt appropriate security measure so as to prevent the leakage of data and damage to right owner’s interests. Please pay great attention to protecting your own or other’s data information. You shall refrain from disclosing the data information to the public without authorization. <br> <b>(c) The information we obtain during your use of Our Products and services </b> <br> In order to provide high-quality services to you, Our Products collect information for the purpose of performing the product service contract based on the need of Our Products collecting the information from images and documents you upload. We may record and analyze the use and the method of use of our services and any other relevant information, including hardware model and identification information, operating system version, system activities and other device information, Internet Protocol address, account sign-in or sign-out, clicks of advertisements and other log information, as well as Web Beacon or Cookies, browser version information. You may manage permission through security software and we will try our best to seek a balance between your permission and your experience, for instance that we may inform you of authorizing when you first use relevant functions, but then we will no longer inform you frequently to avoid affecting your  experience. However, you may not use the products to achieve the purpose of net social if you disagree with the authorization. The purpose of collecting the information of installing applications is only for analyzing which other products would be selected for use by our clients with Our Products. The information of operating system, etc. is collected for security of the products, which can be in the form of security tip to you. <br> Including the information mentioned above, the information we collect and/or use include user personal information, non-user personal information, the information recorded by third party’s platform, etc. <br> You agree that the scope of information we collect mentioned above can be properly adjusted with development of legal and regulatory provisions, development of technology and business and user’s feedback, etc. </p>    <hr id=\"access-to-review-and-update-of-personal-information\"> <h3>VI. Access to, review and update of personal information</h3> <p>You can access, review and update (to ensure that we can timely reach you when necessary, you should process some update upon change of the information) your personal information; However, for the sake of security, you may only do so after you log in. In case of any changes to your personal information, you shall timely log in your account and update accordingly.</p>   <hr id=\"cancellation-of-personal-account\"> <h3>VII. Cancellation of personal account</h3> <p>You may contact us at [support@Evizcards.com] to cancel your account. We will respond to your request within a reasonable time. After cancelation of your account, we are not obliged to keep or provide information under your account. Except as otherwise provided by law, we will delete your personal information if so requested by you.</p>   <hr id=\"use-and-setting-of-personal-information\"> <h3>VIII. Use and setting of personal information</h3> <p>By using Our Products and services, you consent to and grant authorization to our collection and processing your information, including the device and software user information, personal information and content information uploaded by user (mainly the image information you uploaded; regarding the uploaded content, you warrant that you have the intellectual property involved therein or have obtained the relevant license and there is no infringement of third party’s right). The information is only used for the optimization of software interface interaction. No specific information will be used or disclosed. <br> You understand and agree that the information you make public (because of your own choice or our default setting, e.g. the document or user name you share) may be browsed, reposted and commented by other users of our services. You may protect your critical information by deciding whether to upload certain information, and whether to turn on the specific function of Our Products. To prevent harassment due to abuse of personal information by others, we suggest you pay attention and soon familiarize yourself with the function setting of Our Products. The default setting is offered in consideration of various factors including industry customs, general need of most users and product form, etc. It is possible that what suits most users does not meet your particular need.<b> YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT, GIVEN THAT THE SERVICES WE PROVIDE INCLUDE SOCIAL NETWORKING WEB SERVICES, THE DEFAULT SETTING OF OUR PRODUCTS MAY MAKE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AVAILABLE TO THE PUBLIC IN ORDER TO IMPROVE USER EXPERIENCE, AND SUCH DEFAULT SETTING MAY ENABLE ANY OTHER PERSON TO HAVE ACCESS TO OR OBTAIN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.</b> <br> Your personal registration information, including but not limited to accounts, username and any other information set by you as sharable, will be seen by users with whom you share documents or collaborate. The shared information is for the sole purpose of identification of the owner of the document. <br> <b>Our Products will ask for the following permissions during regular operation:</b> <br> 1. Storage: Access to device storage in order to read and manage documents <br> 2. Camera & Album: Using your device’s camera and photo album to take photos for the function of auto crop <br> 3. Contacts: Accessing device contacts for the function of user inviting (if you don’t use the collaboration function, this permission will not be asked) <br> 4. Phone: Accessing the equipment ID for bounding Premium Membership to your device or for use without sign-in. <br> 5. Cookies: When accessing our webpage <a href=\"https://evizcards.com\">(www.Evizcards.com)</a>, we use cookies to provide you with necessary services. <br> It is required to grant these permissions otherwise the stated functions may not work as intended. As more functions are added to our product, We may require your permission and we will ask your approval before accessing your data.</p>   <hr id=\"disclosure-of-and-making-available-to-public-the-personal-identity-information\"> <h3>IX. Disclosure of and making available to public the personal identity information</h3> <p>We respect and protect your privacy and undertake that we will not disclose a user’s personal identity information to any third-party entity or person except as stated in the Privacy Policy, unless: <br> 1. You agree to make your personal information available to public including but not limited to in the default setting or other setting you adjusted the Products to; <br> 2. User’s personal information is provided according to law, or required by governmental or judicial authority; or <br> 3. In case of emergency and where necessary, the information is required to be disclosed in order to protect the lawful rights and interests of EVIZCARDS or other users or the public security and public interest. <br> Under the circumstances described in the above Sub-clauses 2 and 3, we will do our best to notify you on the disclosure. You understand and agree that the notification to you will be made in the principles of promptness and integrity,<b> BUT IF IT CANNOT BE TIMELY MADE DUE TO OBJECTIVE FACTOR OR FOR REASONABLE CAUSE, WE WILL NOT ASSUME ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THAT.</b></p>  <hr id=\"privacy-protection-in-bankruptcy-sale-merger\"> <h3>X. Privacy protection in bankruptcy/sale/merger</h3> <p>In case of sale of company assets, merger with another business entity or bankruptcy filing, etc., the information we collect in providing services may be assigned as part of our assets, and any other entity assigned with this part of assets may continue to use the information according to law and the Privacy Policy. <br> If your trust in us changes upon the abovementioned assignment, you can cancel your account according to the existing rules.</p>    <hr id=\"privacy-terms-applicable-to-juveniles\"> <h3>XI. Privacy terms applicable to juveniles</h3> <p>We pay great attention to the security and protection of juveniles’ privacy and data. We will be unable to identify whether the user is a juvenile unless we are expressly notified of the same. We will neither use personal information of juveniles nor disclose personal identity information of juveniles to any third-party, if we are informed that the user is a juvenile, unless for the purpose of providing necessary and emergent help or as stipulated herein. If any guardian or interested party of the juvenile finds that there is issue of juvenile’s information involved in Our Products, please contact us via our customer service support to file complaint at support@Evizcards.com. Upon verification and concluding we have the issue, we will soonest possible delete information, cancel account or respond otherwise as required. If development of relevant legislation has new demand for protection of juvenile’s privacy, we will take further action soonest possible and ensure our strict compliance in operation.</p>   <hr id=\"law-and-Jurisdiction\"> <h3>XII. Law and Jurisdiction</h3> <p>EVIZCARDS will provide protection to privacy and personal information according to the Privacy Policy made according to law. <b>WHEN YOU BROWSE OR USE OUR PRODUCTS, YOU AGREE THAT YOU (AND YOUR ACT OF BROWSING AND USING) WILL BE REGULATED BY THE PRC LAWS AND YOU CONSENT TO JURISDICTION OF THE PRC COURT. THE PARTIES AGREE THAT THE RELEVANT DISPUTE SHOULD BE FIRST RESOLVED THROUGH NEGOTIATION, FAILING WHICH, IT IS TO BE SUBMITTED TO THE COMPETENT COURT AT EVIZCARDS DOMICILE.</b></p>    <hr id=\"risks-and-exemption\"> <h3>XIII. Risks and exemption</h3> <p>If your personal information or privacy is leaked due to any of the following causes, we will use our best efforts to remedy or assist you, provided, however, that you shall agree that we are not liable for: <br> 1. Information divulged due to computer virus, trojan and hacker attack; <br> 2. Personal information divulged because you tell your password to others, cause others to have your password, or share a registered account with others; or <br> 3. Any other divulgence of personal information not caused by reason of Evizcards. </p>   <hr id=\"storage-of-personal-information\"> <h3>XIV. Storage of personal information</h3> <p>The information we collect may be stored and processed by Evizcards or its affiliates or service providers through their servers. As Our Products can be downloaded and used by users worldwide, the servers may be located in Australia or India (for the purpose of this clause, It may be located on one of the Cloud services provide whose Servers are located worldwide) or other country/region based on the need of providing the service.<p>  <hr id=\"implementation-of-Privacy-Policy\"> <h3>XV. Implementation of Privacy Policy</h3> <p>We will regularly inspect the implementation of the Privacy Policy. If you have any questions, suggestions, complaints or reports about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at the e-mail address, support@Evizcards.com with the e-mail subject: Issues about Privacy Policy.</p>    </div>      </div>    <!-- main container ends -->  </div>     </body>  </html>]]></string>
    <string name="terms_text"></string>
    <string name="terms_text1"><![CDATA[<!DOCTYPE html> <html>    <!-- body -->  <body>    <!-- main container --> <div class=\"container-fluid\">      <!-- Terms --> <div class=\"row justify-content-center bgf5\" id=\"terms&conditions\">      <!-- scroller list -->  <div class=\"col-sm-12 col-md-12 col-lg-12 align-content-center justify-content-center\" id=\"termsConditions\">      <a class=\"scroller headScroll\" href=\"#terms\">TERMS & CONDITIONS</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#products\">PRODUCTS</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#software-licence-and-service\">Scope of Software License and Service</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#paid-service\">Paid Service</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#registration-and-account-security\">Registration and Account Security</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#privacy-and-personal-information\">Privacy and Personal Information</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#providing-services-as-is\">Providing Services “As Is”</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#information-push\">Information Push</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#third-party-services\">Third Party Services</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#content-generated-by-user\">Content Generated by User</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#information-storage-and-synchronization\">Information Storage and Synchronization</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#code-of-conduct-for-users\">Code of Conduct for Users</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#intellectual-property-rights\">Intellectual Property Rights</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#limitation-of-liability\">Limitation of Liability</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#use-by-juveniles\">use by juveniles</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#notifications\">Notification of Infringed Contents</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#effectiveness-rerm-and-renewal\">Effectiveness, Term and Renewal</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#amendment\">amendment</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#update-discontinuation-suspension-and-termination\">Update, Discontinuation, Suspension and Termination</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#severability\">severability</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#governing-law-and-jurisdiction\">governing law and jurisdiction</a> \t<a class=\"scroller\" href=\"#miscellaneous\">miscellaneous</a>   \t<a id=\"backToTop\" href=\"#terms&conditions\"><i class=\"fa fa-arrow-alt-circle-up\"></i></a>       </div>  <!-- text -->  <div class=\"col-sm-12 col-md-12 col-lg-12 align-content-center justify-content-center\" id=\"termsConditions\">  <hr id=\"terms\"> <h3>TERMS & CONDITIONS</h3> <p>Please read these terms and conditions of use carefully before accessing, using or obtaining any materials, information, products or services. By accessing, the Evizcards website, mobile or tablet application, or any feature or the other Evizcards platform (collectively “Our Website”) you agree to be bound these terms and conditions (“Terms”) and our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept all these terms, then you may not use our website. In these terms, “we”, “us”, “our” or “EVIZCARDS” refers to Evizcards software corporation, and “you” or “your” refers to you as the user of our website. <br> <b>THESE TERMS INCLUDE AN ARBITRATION CLAUSE AND A WAIVER OF YOUR RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION OR REPRESENTATIVE LAWSUIT.</b> <br> We may modify these Terms, for any reason at any time, by posting a new version on our website, these changes do not affect rights and obligations that arose to such changes. Your continued use of Our Website following the posting of modified Terms will be subject to the terms in effect at the time of your use. Please review these Terms periodically for changes. If you object to any provision of these Terms or any subsequent modifications to these terms or become a dissatisfied with Our Website in any way, your only recourse is to immediately terminate use of Our Website.</p>   <hr id=\"products\"> <h3>1. Our Products</h3> <p>For the purpose of the Terms of Service, “Our Products” refer to “EVIZCARDS” and services (provided by our company and/or our branches, affiliates or partners across the globe) in connection with the software products. <br> “EVIZCARDS” refers to software with functions of documents scan, recognition and administration and other related internet-based value-added services (“Our Service”). We provide the above-mentioned services through free or paid EVI ZCARDS software (“Our Software”), EVIZCARDS website (http://www.evizcards.com), or application programming interfaces (“APIs”) for third parties to use. We specially remind you that we only provide you the software and service as tools. When using our products acquiring and processing information, you should respect legal rights of others such as intellectual property rights, personal information and privacy rights, etc., and make sure that you are authorized to copy , amend, upload and publish the information. If you upload or publish the information without permission, you may infringe legal rights of others and be legally liable for it.</p>   <hr id=\"software-licence-and-service\"> <h3>II. Scope of Software License and Service</h3> <p>We grant you or your specified users a personal, worldwide, revocable, nontransferable and non-exclusive license to use our products. Unless otherwise expresslyagreed in writing, you are permitted to install, use, display or run Our Software or use Our Services on your smart mobile end-device, including but not, smart phone,  scanner, and PC as well as other computer system (“end -device”) for non-commercial purposes.</p>   <hr id=\"paid-service\"> <h3>III. Paid Service</h3> <p>You may need to pay for some services of Our Products. You (and your specified users) will acquire relevant services with the fees duly paid in full. For paid service, we will obtain your consent before collection of payment. <br> EVIZCARDS could make changes about payment standard and method according to practical needs. Some free services may become paid services in the fu ture. If the fee is not paid on time and in full, you will no longer be able to use the service when we start to charge fees. The above-mentioned change will be notified or published on our websites or reminded during a period of time before you use releva nt services. The price of the products provided through website may change at any time. If there is a price reduction or promotion, EVIZCARDS will not provide price protection or refund your payment. <br> As the software products contains information of authorization and activation (including but not limited to activation code, password, etc.) and are special commodities due to the risk of the information being revealed for others to open accounts, the policy on return of goods without any reason is not applicab le after the transaction is completed. If no major quality problems, no return or exchange will be allowed. If you have any inquires or need any assistance, you can send email to <b>support@evizcards.com</b>. </p>   <hr id=\"registration-and-account-security\"> <h3>IV. Registration and Account Security</h3> <p>In order to better use EVIZCARDS service, we suggest you create an EVIZCARDS account and sign in with this account when you use Our Products and service. You commit that the information you provide when registering the EVIZCARDDS account is true and bear the adverse consequences and any loss of us or third parties resulting from providing false information. When you apply for opening certain service, we will verify your identity. You commit that you will cooperate actively with us, otherwise you will not be able to use these services. <br> Please keep the password of your EVIZCARDS account secure. You agree that you will bear full responsibility for any and all the activities under your EVIZCARDS account. In order to keep your EVIZCARDS account secure, we particularly remind you of taking certain measures including but not limited to safekeeping your password, installing anti-virus/Trojan software, changing your password regularly and logging out safely after use, etc. If your account or password is stolen, you shall assume full  responsibility for all the consequences arising therefrom unless you can prove that it is caused by our intentional act or gross negligence. <br> Your EVIZCARDS account can only be used by yourself and cannot be shared with others; otherwise we cannot ensure your data security. You understand and agree that any act done with your EVIZCARDS account is considered as yours, and you will be jointly and severally liable even if the case is others use your EVIZCARDS account to perform the act. If you learn of any unauthorized use of your account, or password, please contact and notify us immediately: support@evizcards.com.</p>   <hr id=\"privacy-and-personal-information\"> <h3>V. Privacy and Personal Information</h3> <p>We respect the privacy and personal information of each user and will protect your privacy and personal information in accordance with applicable law, especially special law/regulation on data protection by taking necessary measures and comply with the same in collecting, processing, transmitting and storing your personal information. Please be sure to read carefully our Privacy Policy which specifies the way we collect and use your personal information, etc. <br> We particularly remind that the information you upload may involve other people ’s personal information or privacy. We will not disclose such contents without authorization. <br> You understand and undertake that you will fully respect any other persons’ privacy that you learn, receive or have access to from the information of other users and you will fully respect any other persons’ privacy in the information you upload as well. You will never collect, duplicate, store, disseminate, spread or misuse others’ private information without permission. If you obtain, use, sell or spread other’s personal information in bad faith, or infringe other’s privacy in any other way (including but not limited to harassment), you are in material breach of this Agreement. We will be entitled to at any time restrict or terminate your account privilege up to delete your account and we reserve the right to unilaterally terminate this Agreement and demand you to bear legal liabilities. <br> Special reminder: As mobile phone number is usually tied up with quite many functions used as tool for identification assistance, if your mobile phone number changes, please timely revise the relevant content of your account so that others may not clear identification test by using your mobile phone without permission. You should take precaution and deal with that situation accordingly when the email address for identity verification has security issue.</p> <br> <h6>Our Products will ask for the following permissions during regular operation:</h6> <ul> <li>Storage: Access to device storage in order to read and manage documents;</li> <li>Camera & Album: Use your device’s camera and photo album to take photos for the auto crop function;</li> <li>Contacts: Access device contacts for inviting users to collaborate;</li> <li>Phone: Binding the premium membership to your device ID to automatically log you in;</li> <li>Location Services: we need to access your location to provide you with certain functions such as “Electronic Evidence”;</li> <li>Cookies: When accessing our webpage (www.evizcards.com), we use cookies to provide you with necessary services.</li> </ul> <p><b>Permission will not be asked if you do not use these functions. If additional authority is required, we will ask for your permission in advance.</b></p>    <hr id=\"providing-services-as-is\"> <h3>VI. Providing Services “As Is”</h3> <p>Our Products and services are provided on the basis of a currently available level of skill and condition. We are trying our best to meet your needs and ensure the consistency and security of our services. But we are not able to foresee at all times some legal and technological risks including but no t limited to service interruption, data loss and other damages and risks due to force majeure, viruses, Trojans, hackers’ attack, unstable system, defective services provided by third parties, and government actions. <br> <b>You hereby acknowledge and confirm that you use Our Products and services at your own risk, except as otherwise provided by law.</b></p>   <hr id=\"information-push\"> <h3>VII. Information Push</h3> <p>You agree that you may receive information pushed out when using Our Products and services that include update of Our Products or services and information of third party’s products or services that may be helpful to you, etc.] <br> We specially remind that if the information pushed out you receives is about third party and not us, regarding such information; you should make your own judgment on authenticity of the content and be responsible for your own judgment and act. <b>Except as expressly provided by law, we are not liable in any way for any loss or damage borne by you due to the content provided by way of such information.</b></p>   <hr id=\"third-party-services\"> <h3>VIII. Third Party Services</h3> <p>In Our Products, we allow you to invoke services provided by third parties, social website or email services, etc. We only invoke services from third parties in our products through APIs and actual services are provided by third parties. For terms of use and relevant provisions, please refer to the terms of service, etc. issued by those third parties. We will urge the third parties to comply with the applicable laws and regulations on personal information protection when they provide services. We do not bear any direct or indirect liability for any problem of personal information protection  that happens in your using third party services or loss caused therefrom and the problem or loss should be borne by you and/or relevant liable party.</p>   <hr id=\"content-generated-by-user\"> <h3>IX. Content Generated by User</h3> <p>The contents provider should assume liability for any content (including but not limited to image file, file information, contact list, business card information, geographic location, email, message, material, literary works, software, music, sound recording, photo, graph, video, data, user’s registration information or other information, etc., “Contents”), whether transmitted in public or in private via Our Products. You (or your designated users) warrant that you (or your designated users) have ne cessary authorization to upload such Contents. If your (or your designated user’s) acts cause losses (including but not limited to compensation, attorney fees) to EVIZCARDS, <b>you agree to fully compensate for the losses.</b> We reserve the right to review, block and delete the Contents or terminate the services pursuant to law. <br> As to the publicized contents, unless you notify us the contrary intention in writing, and it is not against law/regulation on personal data protection, <b>you agree to grant EVIZCARDS the world-wide, royalty-free, non-exclusive, sub-licensable and permanent license to use the same. We may decide at our own discretion to use (including but not limited to reproduce, adapt, amend, create derivative works, and translate) and distribute these Contents. In the meanwhile you authorize EVIZCARDS to file any action in its own name against any third party for the infringement upon the foregoing Contents and any of its derivative works and to receive all the compensation. You shall warrant that you have necessary authorization to grant such license to EVIZCARDS.</b> <br> Notwithstanding the foregoing provision of reservation of rights, we will not necessarily use or distribute the Contents. Furthermore, such reservation of rights is only applicable to the Contents you have publicized rather than any personal information or privacy which has not yet been publicized. Unless otherwise provided in law/regulation on data protection, without permission of right holder, we will not use or provide to third party the unpublicized personal information and privacy. <br> You should be owner of copyright, or holder of other rights that should be had for using the services as to the lawful contents you post in the services.</p>  <hr id=\"information-storage-and-synchronization\"> <h3>X. Information Storage and Synchronization</h3> <p>1. You acknowledge and agree to store information relating to use of Our Products into your own end-device, which will occupy some room of the end-device. EVIZCARDS reminds that you should make your choice as to whether to set passwords for using Our Services in order to protect information security according to your needs. <br> 2. You acknowledge and agree that the information generated during your use of Our Products may be stored and processed by EVIZCARDS or its affiliates or service providers through their servers. As Our Products can be downloaded and used by users worldwide, the servers may be located in India (for the purpose of this clause, excluding HK, Macao and Taiwan) or other countries/regions based on the need of providing the service, in compliance with laws and regulations. <br> 3. If you use Our Products and sign in your account at your end -device, the information already stored in the end-device if expressly confirmed by you will be added to your account and stored in EVIZCARDS servers. Your account will be bound to the end-device as a default status and you can unbind the account and the end -device in the setting by logging out the account. <br> 4. When you use Our Products after signing in your account, any direct modification of information in end-device (if stored in our server according to the preceding section) or modification of information in account via web end will be synchronized automatically between end-device and server in its lately modified form. Therefore, if you are using an end-device which is not owned by you, please be sure to log out timely and make necessary adjustment to your settings so as to avoid any leakage of personal information or privacy of yours or others. <br> 5. If there is loss of information because you accidentally delete the information in end-device or server account, you could visit our websites and sign in your account to restore your information. <br> 6. EVIZCARDS system stores, backups and provides recovery of information based on your operation. You should read operation guidelines carefully to well understand the default setting of the system and adjust it at your own will so as to use Our Products in a proper way. We remind that even if we will take necessary measures to store and protect your data, you should backup your data on your own. EVIZCARDS shall not be responsible for picture and other information you delete or fail to successfully store.</p>    <hr id=\"code-of-conduct-for-users\"> <h3>XI. Code of Conduct for Users</h3> <p>1. You shall abide by local laws and regulations during your use of Our Products, and you shall not produce, duplicate, publicize or release sensitive information, illegal information or any information or material which a normal person considers immoral, including but not limited to the information: <br> i. Contravening the basic principles determined by the Constitution; <br> ii. Endangering national safety, divulging state secret, overturning state power and sabotaging national unity; <br> iii. Damaging national reputation and interests; <br> iv. Instigating ethnic hatred, discrimination and sabotaging ethnic unity; v. Sabotaging national religious policies and advocating heresy and feudalistic superstition; <br> vi. Spreading rumours to disturb social order and sabotaging social stability; <br> vii. Spreading obscenity, eroticism, gambling, violence, murder, terrorism or subornation; <br> viii. Insulting or slandering other person or infringement upon other person’s legal rights; <br> ix. Containing any other Contents which are prohibited by laws and administrative regulations; or <br> x. Other Contents which are in violation to the Cyber Security Law of the People’s Australia. <br> 2. You shall not use Our Products for any illegal purpose or use the same to conduct any illegal activities, including but not limited to: <br> i. Using Our Products to carry out any acts which may adversely affect normal operation of the Internet; <br> ii. Embezzling, gaining illegal access to or abusing other user’s account or information contained in such account; <br> iii. Falsifying facts maliciously, or concealing truth to mislead and deceive others; <br> iv. Publishing, transmitting, spreading advertising information and junk information; <br> initiating, continuing or taking part in any speculation or illegal activity in any way, or utilizing telephone, network and any other communication means to harass other person; <br> v. Releasing, spreading, disseminating, storing the contents which infringe upon the intellectual property and trade secrets of others; <br> or spreading or distributing or otherwise spreading any document containing any picture, photo, software or other data which is protected by intellectual property law, unless you have corresponding rights, authorization or have obtained necessary approva l; <br> or vi. Any other acts prohibited by laws and regulations. <br> 3. You shall not engage in any activity jeopardizing the legitimate interests of EVIZCARDS. Unless expressly provided by law or EVIZCARDS has consented in writing, you shall not conduct any acts not expressly authorized under these Terms of Service during the use of Our Products, including but not limited to: <br> i. Deleting all the information regarding the copyright of Our Products; <br> ii. Conduct any reverse engineering, disassembling or de -compilation against the Software or otherwise attempting to find the source code of Our Products; <br> iii. Duplicating, amending, altering or mounting the information of Our Products for commercial purpose (including but not limited to any information in the Software an d any information stored in any terminal device during the use of Our Products, as well as the information interacted between the client and server), or creating any derivative works or products with the same in any form including but not limited to using plug-in, add-on or third party tool/service to connect with, disturb or affect Our Products and related system; <br> iv. Restricting, prohibiting or otherwise interfering in or affecting any other person’s use or enjoyment the services of Our Products (except f or such safe and protection tools as parental control), including but not limited to releasing or transmitting any information or software in the following nature: the information or software including worm, virus or any other harmful function, or the traffic of which so generated may impede the using, sending or searching of information by others; <br> v. Having access to or attempting to have access to Our Products by any automatic means, or violating the requirements of any robots.txt or similar documents in the related program of the software or services of Our Products; <br> vi. Using, leasing, borrowing, reproduction of data, amending, linking, reposting, assembling, releasing, publishing and establishing of mirror image station of information and Contents of Our Products for commercial purpose; <br> vii. Carrying out any operation for the purpose of manipulation or distortion, making any rating or comment which may damage Our Products, or conducting any acts that may affect the completeness or accuracy of the service s of Our Products; or <br> viii. Any other acts without the express authorization of EVIZCARDS. <br> 4. <b>If you conduct any of the foregoing acts, you should solely undertake related liabilities and we are not liable. If any damage is thus caused, you should make compensation according to law, and we reserve the rights of recovery of losses and demand of compensation according to law.</b> <br> 5. <b>You agree to indemnify and hold harmless EVIZCARDS from and against any losses incurred to EVIZCARDS arising from your violation of these Terms of Service, including but not limited to any claims of, demands or losses made by any third party arising from or resulting from your acts, and our necessary expenses of dealing with related matters, such as attorney’s fee.</b> <br> 6. You undertake that you will abide by and guide and supervise your specified users to abide by local laws and regulations, relevant Terms of Service and Privacy Policy when using Our Products.</p>   <hr id=\"intellectual-property-rights\"> <h3>XII. Intellectual Property Rights</h3> <p>You acknowledge and agree that EVIZCARDS possesses any and all the lawful rights and interests of Our Products, including any intellectual property rights involved in the software and service. <br> The information in Our Products includes but not limited to words, software, audios and videos, photos, diagrams, all contents in advertisements, the commercial information we offer to you, etc., which are all protected under copyright, patent, trademark as well as all other related laws and regulations. You are allowed to use these contents only when you have our authorization; no unauthorized reproduction, modification or compilation of these contents or creations of relevant derivative works are permitted. <br> Unless you have otherwise reached written agreement with EVIZCARDS, this Agreement does not authorize you to use name of software, trademark, service mark, logo, domain name or any other sign with distinctive brand feature relating to EVIZCARDS.</p>    <hr id=\"limitation-of-liability\"> <h3>XIII. Limitation of Liability</h3> <p>1. Please directly visit our websites to download the installation program of the software or learn any other safe downloading channels we have authorized. You (and your specified users) are required to create account and use Our S ervice through the official channels we provide, including the use of the software or visit to our websites. We are unable to guarantee the safety of your software, services and account if you are in violation of the aforementioned requirements on download ing and installation. In addition, we will not be liable for any loss incurred to you or any third party due to your use of unauthorized software, service or account. <br> 2. You are required to use Our Products in a proper way. For the detailed functions and operations, please see the content of “Help” in the products. You may also contact us directly to obtain necessary help: support@evizcards.com. You will be liable for any losses due to your improper setting or improper operation. <br> 3. You fully understand that Our Products will involve Internet services and may encounter various risks such as force majeure which may cause the suspension of relevant services. We will use our best efforts to conduct timely repair, howsoever you shall be solely responsible for all losses incurred thereby, and we are not liable for the losses. Such risks include but not limited to the service interruption and disruption as a result of any of the following reasons: <br> 1) Damage due to computer virus, Trojan or other malicious program, and hacker attack; <br> 2) A fault takes place in the software, system, hardware or communication lines of the terminal device of the users or EVIZCARDS; <br> 3) Accident, natural disaster or governmental act; <br> 4) Users’ use of any services which are not provided or authorized by EVIZCARDS; or <br> 5) Any other force majeure or factor beyond EVIZCARDS control. <br> 4. We will not provide any guaranty of any kind for any unpredictable or <br> uncontrollable technical defect in the product, service stability and any losses or damages thereby caused, unless otherwise required by law or regulation. <br> 5. EVIZCARDS reminds that you should export your photo information and backup regularly. <br> 6. We will not be directly or indirectly liable if there is any direct or indirect loss incurred during the period when Our Products are not available for normal use.</p>   <hr id=\"use-by-juveniles\"> <h3>XIV. Use by Juveniles</h3> <p>Our Products does not directly target any juvenile users. If you are a juvenile user and decide to use Our Products any way, please first seek the consent of your guardian and/or other adult with guardianship duties and use Our Products under the guidance and supervision of your guardian or any other adult with guardianship duties. In addition, your guardian and/or other adult with guardianship duties shall be responsible for assisting you in correctly understanding the contents of this Agreement and other related legal documents in order to guide you to use Our Products in a correct way.<p>  <hr id=\"notifications\"> <h3>XV. Notification of Infringed Contents and Counter Notification Procedures</h3> <p>1. Infringement Notification: As part of our intellectual protection work, except for the provisions of the Terms of Service, if any individual or group finds that any other user has infringed upon its lawful rights or interests by transmitting information through the use of our services, such individual or group (“Complainant”) may notify us in writing by giving us an official infringement notification signed or stamped (if it is a duly established organization or entity) for the purpose of protecting intellectual property rights. The infringement notification will include the following contents: detailed contact information of the Complainant, including the name, address, telephone number and email address with a copy of the ID card, passport or registration certificate; contents of suspected infringement as shown in this service for our notifying the user who manages the contents; materials as preliminary proof of infringement act; <br> a) Ownership certificates to certify Complainant’s trademark rights, copyrights and other exercisable rights to the Contents pursuant to law in respect of the Contents of suspected infringement; <br> b) Specifying the contents of the suspected infringement which has infringed upon the Complainant’s legitimate interests set forth in Section a) above; <br> c) The infringement notification shall also include the following statement: “(i) I am the oblige or I am authorized to exercise the rights; (ii) I hereby represent that the information contained in the infringement notification is adequate, true and accurate, and I am the oblige of the statutory rights specified in Section a) of this infringement notification or I am authorized to exercise such rights. My lawful rights and interests are infringed upon by the Contents contained in the web page which are suspected of infringement; and (iii) I hereby confirm that if anything contained in this infringement notification is untrue, I would be liable for such misrepresentation”. <br> 2. Counter Notification: If we remove your Contents or links based on the infringement notification, you may submit to us an official written counter notification signed or stamped (if it is a duly established organization or entity). Your counter notification shall be made in the following format including detailed contact information, including the name, address, telephone number and email address with a copy of the ID card, passport or registration certificate; the information, contents or web pages removed by us; materials as preliminary proof of non-infringement; <br> a) The materials which can prove the legality of the Contents removed, including but not limited to the materials which can prove your rights to the Contents removed or that you have been authorized to exercise the rights to the Contents removed; <br> b) The counter notification shall also include the following statement: “(i) I am the oblige or I am authorized to exercise the rights; (ii) I have the right or am authorized to provide or release the information or Contents removed ; I hereby represent that the information contained in the counter notification is adequate, true and accurate, and I am the oblige of the statutory rights specified in Section a) of the counter notification or I am authorized to exercise such rights; and (iii) I hereby confirm that if anything contained in this counter notification is untrue, I would be liable for such misrepresentation”. <br> 3. Please send the foregoing materials and your contact information to support@evizcards.com. <br> 4. We will process your request forthwith upon receipt of the valid infringement notification and counter notification according to law. You agree that we can copy the notification and attached supporting documents and provide that to third party to find out about the facts involved. We will also contact you on the mater via phone, email, etc</p>   <hr id=\"effectiveness-rerm-and-renewal\"> <h3>XVI. Effectiveness, Term and Renewal</h3> <p>By using and registration with Our Products, you express your consent to and acceptance of this Agreement, i.e. this Agreement will be binding upon you. If you do not agree with this Agreement, please stop using Our Products immediately.</p>   <hr id=\"amendment\"> <h3>XVII. Amendment</h3> <p>We have the right to amend the provisions of this Agreement from time to time subject to the change of law and regulative policy and based on need of operation and development. If such amendments result in material reduction of your rights under this Agreement, before the amendments come into effect, we will notify you via reminder in distinct spot at the interface of Our Products, website announcement or email. Your continuous use of Our Products will be deemed as your acceptance of such update.</p>   <hr id=\"update-discontinuation-suspension-and-termination\"> <h3>XVIII. Update, Discontinuation, Suspension and Termination of Our Products</h3> <p>1. You may stop using Our Products at any time. If you want to cancel your account, please contact us: support@evizcards.com. You may send the email regarding cancelation of the account via the registered email address. We will respond as soon as possible within reasonable period. <br> 2. Our Products may be updated from time to time. You may at your own discretion decide whether to accept the updates or not. We do not guarantee providing you with latest updated services if you do not accept the updates, and you shall be solely responsible for any loss that may be incurred. <br> 3. We reserve the rights to amend, interrupt, suspend or terminate to provide Our Products based on the actual situation at any time, which includes but not limited to the memory space obtainable to a single user, the nature and quantity of the contents uploaded and other data or the ability of the users on continuously accessing Our Products and services, etc. We will make reasonable effort to notify you. We will provide high quality services for you and there will be situations described in this section only under special conditions. <br> 4. You agree that we may, without prior notice, suspend or terminate the services if: <br> i. the personal information you provide is inaccurate, fake or illegal/valid; ii. You are in breach of this Agreement; iii. You fail to make sufficient payment to EVIZCARDS (if applicable); iv. We do so subject to law or requirements of competent authority; v. other condition upon which we need to do so. <br> 5. If your account without subscription of any paid service is not in use in successive nine months, we reserve the right to terminate such account (before one month prior to termination, we will notify you on your continuous status of not signing in your account and notify you that if you do not sign in within the following one month, we will terminate the account for use), in order to avoid any waste of resources. The losses (including but not limited to loss of information, etc.) incurred therefrom should be borne by yourself. <br> 6. The account will be cancelled upon termination of Our Service. We, subject to law and regulation, reserve the right to completely delete all information in your account, and we shall no longer undertake obligation to you.</p>   <hr id=\"severability\"> <h3>XIX. Severability</h3> <p>If any provision of these Terms of Service is held to be illegal or unenforceable by any court or arbitral institution, the other provisions shall survive and continue to be binding.</p>   <hr id=\"governing-law-and-jurisdiction\"> <h3>XX. Governing Law and Jurisdiction</h3> <p>1. The parties understand and agree to abide by the special regulations applicable to certain nations/regions as set forth in the <a href=\"\"><b>Privacy Policy.</b></a> <br> 2. The parties agree that the governing law of these Terms of Service as follows: When you browse or use our products, you agree that you (and your act of browsing and using) will be regulated by the Australian laws and you consent to jurisdiction of the Australian court. The parties agree that the relevant dispute should be first resolved through negotiation, failing which; it is to be submitted to the competent court at EVIZCARDS domicile.</p>   <hr id=\"miscellaneous\"> <h3>XXI. Miscellaneous</h3> <p>1. All the headings used in these Terms of Service are inserted only so that the text is easy for reading. They do not have any actual meaning and should not be taken as the basis for the construction of these Terms of Service. <br> 2. With regard to amendment to these Terms of Service, change of services or modification to any other important matters, we will make an announcement through our website or notify you via email, etc. Such no tification shall be deemed as having  been served upon release of the announcement or delivery of the email to your registered email. <br> 3. We welcome your feedback in respect of Our Products. Unless otherwise expressly represented or subject to applicable laws, any feedback sent from you will be deemed as non-confidential contents. You agree that we may, at our own discretion, decide whether to release or publish such contents. And you agree to authorize us to use the same at no cost and to amend, adapt, adjust design or change related technical plans, or make any amendment as necessary. <br> 4. If you have any comments on our services or the Terms of Service, you may contact us: support@evizcards.com, and we will use our best efforts to provide you with timely and necessary assistance.</p>    </div>      </div>       <!-- main container ends -->  </div>   </body>  </html>]]></string>
</resources>